Guide to the Frank Lyon Polk Papers
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Subject Files, 1912-(1915-1921); Series III; 7 linear feet (7 boxes)
  - Mexico
    - Memoranda, draft agreements, and miscellaneous papers re: crossing of troops over U.S.-Mexican boundary, 1916 March 11-22, undated (Box 28, Folder 446)
    - Miscellaneous telegrams (copies), 1916 March 11 - April 11 (Box 28, Folder 447)
    - Leon Canova: memoranda re: availability of naval vessels, 1916 March 15-22 (Box 28, Folder 448)
    - Newton D. Baker: memorandum re: reward for capture of Pancho Villa, 1916 March 29 (Box 28, Folder 449)
    - Telegrams to James Linn Rodgers, special representative of the State Department, Mexico City, 1916 April 20 - August 15 (Box 28, Folder 450)
    - Instructions to Generals Scott and Funston (carbon), 1916 April 26 (Box 28, Folder 451)
    - Letters and memoranda re: use of State Department documents in Robert H. Murray's articles in Harper's Weekly, 1916 May 3 - June 1 (Box 29, Folder 452)
    - "Memorandum of Mexican Note" of 1916 May 22, [1916 post-May 22] (Box 29, Folder 453)
    - Leon Canova: miscellaneous memoranda, 1916 May 25 (Box 29, Folder 454)
    - Marshall Morgan: memorandum, "Our Record in Mexico: 'Patient Non-Intervention' Policy of United States for Nearly Century--No Exception to This Rule in our History--Friendly Spirit and Desire to Promote Closer Relations Repeatedly and Continuously Expressed--Border Outrages Against Americans since Jackson's Time,", [1916 post-May?] (Box 29, Folder 455)
    - Correspondence and memoranda of conversations with Eliseo Arredondo (carbons, copies, drafts), 1916 June 2 - August 9 (Box 29, Folder 456)
    - William Phillips: memorandum re: U.S. representation in Mexico, 1916 June 21 (Box 29, Folder 457)
    - Harold Walker: memoranda to Polk, 1916 June 24, July 16 (Box 29, Folder 458)
    - Leon Canova: memorandum to Lansing re: U.S. policy toward the Carranza government (carbon), 1916 June 28 (Box 29, Folder 459)
    - Memorandum, "President Wilson's Mexican Policy" (edited), [1916 June - Nov?] (Box 29, Folder 460)
    - Correspondence re: staffing the American and Mexican Joint Commission, 1916 July 15 - August 9 (Box 29, Folder 461)
    - Memorandum re: "The Mazatlan Incident" (carbon), 1916 July 26 (Box 29, Folder 462)
    - Leon Canova: memorandum re: activities of Victoriano Huerta in 1914, 1916 August 3 (Box 29, Folder 463)
    - Leon Canova: "Memorandum: Cases in which representations have been made to the de facto Government of Mexico, since June 20, 1916, and which are still most unsatisfactorily pending" (underlined carbon with covering letter), 1916 August 16, 17 (Box 29, Folder 464)
    - Official communications between the American and Mexican Commissioners of the American and Mexican Joint Commission (copies), 1916 September 22 - November 22 (Box 29, Folder 465)
    - List of U.S. citizens killed by Mexicans in Mexico, 1901 Sep 1 - 1909 Mar 4, compiled for Senator Owen, 1916 October 27 (Box 29, Folder 466)
    - Miscellaneous papers re: the American and Mexican Joint Commission, 1916 November 22-24 (Box 29, Folder 467)
    - William Phillips: memorandum of conversation with Thomas B. Hohler re: safety of foreigners in Mexico, 1916 November 27 (Box 29, Folder 468)
    - Leo S. Rowe: letters and memoranda re: the American and Mexican Joint Commission (copies, photostats), 1916 December 17 - 1917 January 1 (Box 29, Folder 469)
    - Official communications between the American Commissioners and the Mexican Commissioners of the American and Mexican Joint Commission (copies, photostats), 1916 December 18 - 1917 January 6 (Box 29, Folder 469)
    - American Commissioners of the American and Mexican Joint Commission: communications to the President (copies), 1917 January 3, 17 (Box 29, Folder 469)
    - Memoranda re: conversation between Polk and Dr. Harvey about medical assistance for Francisco Villa, 1917 January 10 (Box 29, Folder 470)
    - Fred K. Nielsen: memorandum re: the new Mexican Constitution, 1917 January 22 (Box 29, Folder 471)
    - Harold Walker: memorandum transmitting extracts from the new Mexican Constitution, 1917 February 12 (Box 29, Folder 472)
    - [Ralph W. S. Hill?]: memorandum re: the new Mexican Constitution, 1917 March 27 (Box 29, Folder 473)
    - "Memorandum of Agreement between the United States of America, Party of the First Part - Bankers of New York, London and Paris, Party of the Second Part, - and the Republic of Mexico, Party of the Third Part" (copy) and related correspondence, 1917 April 5 - November 22 (Box 29, Folder 474)
    - Thomas B. Hohler: memorandum re: financial situation of the Mexican government, 1917 July 16 (Box 29, Folder 475)
    - Richard C. Tanis: memoranda re: conversation with W. G. Campbell about acquisition of Lower California, 1917 July 21 (Box 29, Folder 476)
    - Report, correspondence, and memorandum re: sisal, 1917 November 9 - 1918 August 3 (Box 29, Folder 477)
    - A. Iselin and Co: correspondence with the President of the Monetary Commission of Mexico (photostats), 1917 November 14-26 (Box 29, Folder 478)
    - Cables exchanged with the American Embassy, Mexico City, 1917 (Box 29, Folder 479)
    - Miscellaneous papers, 1917 (Box 29, Folder 480)
    - Miscellaneous papers re: export licenses, 1918 January 5 - December 13 (Box 29, Folder 481)
    - Miscellaneous papers re: German vessels in Mexican waters, 1918 February 2 - October 31 (Box 29, Folder 482)
    - Robert Lansing: letters to Ygnacio Bonillas (draft, carbons), 1918 February 12 - April 22 (Box 29, Folder 483)
    - Correspondence, Memoranda, and cables re: bandits, 1918 February 21 - August 27 (Box 29, Folder 484)
    - Eben Richards and William H. Mealy: letter and memorandum re: American bank loan to the Mexican government (carbon, copy), 1918 March 9, April 15 (Box 29, Folder 485)
    - Letter of Mr. Edward L. Doheny to Hon. Mark L.Requa concerning the Importance to the United States of the American Owned Petroleum Properties in Mexico, 1918 March 15 (Box 29, Folder 486)
    - Memoranda, correspondence, and cables re: the Petroleum Decree, 1918 March 19 - November 15 (Box 29, Folder 487)
    - Myron M. Parker: letters re: money and supplies for General Obregon, 1918 April 20 May 20 (Box 29, Folder 488)
    - Gordon Auchincloss: memorandum and draft cable re: Mexican relations with Germany (carbons), 1918 June 4, 24 (Box 29, Folder 489)
    - "Descriptive Statement of Bandit Outrages and Hold-Ups throughout the Tampico Oil Fields," 1917 Aug 15 - 1918 Jul 24 (carbon), [1918 post-July 24] (Box 29, Folder 490)
    - Lewis Warfield: memorandum re: U.S.-Mexican relations, 1918 August 7 (Box 29, Folder 491)
    - J. P. Morgan and Co.: announcement of an international committee of bankers on Mexico (copy), [1918 August - Oct?] (Box 29, Folder 492)
    - Thomas W. Lamont: correspondence re: proposal for an international committee of bankers to represent Mexico's creditors, 1918 October 7 - December 21 (Box 29, Folder 493)
    - Amos L. Beaty, General Counsel, The Texas Company: Rules of American Law Invoked by the Mexican Government in the Amparo Proceedings Brought by the Oil Companies, 1918 October 25 (Box 29, Folder 494)
    - Lester Hood Woolsey: memorandum re: Mexican commission on claims, 1918 November 2, 4 (Box 29, Folder 495)
    - Memorandum of conversation between Polk and James R. Garfield, 1918 Nov 12, [1918 November 12-18] (Box 29, Folder 496)
    - G. Howland Shaw: memorandum of conversation with William Loeb, Jr., and Willard S. Morse re: demands of Pancho Villa on the American Smelting and Refining Company, 1918 November 27 (Box 29, Folder 497)
    - Summaries of recent information from Mexico, 1918 December 10 - 1919 March 1 (Box 29, Folder 498)
    - Elmer R. Jones, Vice President, Wells Fargo and Company Express, S. A.: memorandum and covering letter re: "Mexican Railways and Wells Fargo and Company Express,", 1918 December 23, 27 (Box 29, Folder 499)
    - Boaz Long: memorandum re: kidnapping of alleged Mexican nationals from Douglas, Arizona, 1918 December 28, 29 (Box 29, Folder 500)
    - Cables exchanged with the American Embassy, Mexico City, 1918 (Box 29, Folder 501)
    - Miscellaneous papers, 1918 (Box 29, Folder 502)
    - Boaz Long: memorandum of conversation with C. E. Grunsky, United States Reclamation Service, re: control of the Colorado River, 1919 January 24 (Box 30, Folder 503)
    - Miscellaneous papers re: criticism of Edward L. Doheny's trip to Europe, 1919 February 3 - March 6 (Box 30, Folder 504)
    - Boaz Long: memorandum re: Mexican participation in the Mexican High Commission, 1919 March 13 (Box 30, Folder 505)
    - David Hunter Miller: memorandum re: proposed British mandate for Mexico, 1919 June 20 (Box 30, Folder 506)
    - Memorandum re: "Mexican Activities in Switzerland" (copy), 1919 October 8 (Box 30, Folder 507)
    - Miscellaneous papers, 1919 (Box 30, Folder 508)
    - Memoranda re: drilling new oil wells, 1920 January 2-13 (Box 30, Folder 509)
    - Memorandum re: retention of Louis C. Gilliam on the Mexican Boundary Commission, 1920 March 31, April 1 (Box 30, Folder 510)
    - Memorandum re: claim of Thomas J. Coleman against the Mexican Eagle Oil Company, undated (Box 30, Folder 511)
  - Miscellaneous
    - President of the United States of America: Proclamations, 1915 October 19 - 1918 August 7 (Box 30, Folder 512)
    - President of the United States of America: Proclamations, 1918 August 8 - 1920 March 11 (Box 30, Folder 513)
    - Department of State, Division of Information: Address of the President Delivered to the Senate of the United States, January 22, 1917, 1917 February 14 (Box 30, Folder 514)
    - Department of State, Division of Information: Papers Relating to Maritime Danger Zones and the Placing Belligerents of Mines in the High Seas, Series M, No. 147, 1917 April 4 (Box 30, Folder 515)
    - Cables re: military personnel missing in Europe, 1917 August 24 - 1918 December 16 (Box 30, Folder 516)
    - List of declarations of war, 1914-1917 (mimeo), [post-1917 October 7] (Box 30, Folder 517)
    - Cables re: the mission of Mr. and Mrs. Norman Whitehouse to Switzerland (copies), 1918 January 22 - March 7 (Box 30, Folder 518)
    - Committee on Public Information: Official Bulletin, 1918 August 5 (Box 30, Folder 519)
    - Memorandum re: political opinions of probable delegates to the Peace Conference, [1918 post-September 6] (Box 30, Folder 520)
    - Letters and cables exchanged among members of J. P. Morgan and Co., with State Department intermediaries, 1919 February - June (Box 30, Folder 521)
    - Peace Congress, Paris, 1919. Commission on the the International Regime of Ports, Waterways and Railways. Reports … and Minutes, 1919 February - August (Box 30, Folder 522)
    - Conférence des préliminaires de paix: Composition et fonctionnement, 1919 April 1 (Box 30, Folder 523)
    - American Society of International Law: resolution re: conference to codify international law, 1919 April 17 (Box 30, Folder 523)
    - William C. Redfield: press release of address, "Some Phases of What is called Reconstruction," Cleveland Advertising Club (mimeo), 1919 June 11 (Box 30, Folder 524)
    - Lester H. Woolsey: memorandum re: naturalization treaties, 1919 August 6 (Box 30, Folder 525)
    - Convention portant revision de l'actegénéral de Berlin du 26 février 1885 et del'acte général et de la déclaration de Bruxelles du 2 juillet 1890 signée à Saint-Germain-en-Laye le 10 septembre 1919, [post-1919 September 10] (Box 30, Folder 526)
    - Convention relative au contrôle du commerce des armes et des munitions et protocole signésà Saint-Germain-en-Laye le 10 septembre 1919, [post-1919 September 10] (Box 30, Folder 527)
    - Convention sur le régime des spiritueux en Afrique et protocole signés à Saint-Germain-Laye le10 septembre 1919, [post-1919 September 10] (Box 30, Folder 528)
    - Memorandum re: adjournment of Congress, 1920 June 5 (Box 30, Folder 529)
    - Commission on the Responsibility of the Authors of the War and on the Enforcement of Penalties: Minutes of Meetings of the Commission, undated (Box 30, Folder 530)
    - List of code names for potential Peace Conference participants, undated (Box 30, Folder 531)
    - Memorandum, "Material for an Interview on the Method of Procedure Followed in Making and Rafying [sic] Treaties" (with covering note), undated (Box 30, Folder 532)
    - List of outstanding Peace Conference issues, undated (Box 30, Folder 533)
    - Informal notes in Polk's handwriting, undated (Box 30, Folder 534)
  - Montenegro
    - Miscellaneous exchanges with the minister of Montenegro, 1918 November 23 - December 16 (Box 30, Folder 535)
    - Mémoire sur la restauration de Montenegro (carbon), undated (Box 30, Folder 536)
  - Morocco
    - Memorandum re: recognition of the French protectorate, 1916 July 3 (Box 30, Folder 537)
  - Naval Adviser
    - Memorandum re: distribution of naval war material, 1919 September 13-18 (Box 30, Folder 538)
    - N. A. McCully: memorandum re: "Commissions on which the Naval Adviser is Acting, and their Status,", 1919 September 24 (Box 30, Folder 539)
    - Miscellaneous memoranda, 1919 (Box 30, Folder 540)
  - Navy Department
    - Letters to the Secretary and Assistant Secretary of the Navy (carbons), 1916-1918 (Box 30, Folder 541)
    - Miscellaneous papers, 1916-1918 (Box 30, Folder 542)
  - Near East
    - Arthur J. Balfour: memorandum re: "territorial arrangement of the Turkish Empire outside Europe,", 1919 June 26 (Box 31, Folder 543)
    - Senior U.S. Naval Officer, Turkey; "Report of Operations for Week Ending 17 August 1919,", [1919 post-August 17] (Box 31, Folder 544)
    - Alfred L. P. Dennis: "Memorandum on the Syrian Question,", [1919 August - Sep?] (Box 31, Folder 545)
    - Great Britain, War Cabinet: minutes of meeting with Emir Feisal, Haddad Pasha, and Sheik Fuad of Khatib (copy), 1919 September 23 (Box 31, Folder 546)
    - [Frank L. Polk]: memorandum of conversation with Lloyd George, Churchill, Bonar Law, Allenby, and Milner re: consequences of British withdrawal, [1919 Sep?] (Box 31, Folder 547)
    - David Lloyd George and George N. Curzon: letters to Emir Feisal (copies), 1919 October 9, 10 (Box 31, Folder 548)
    - William Yale: "Report in detail of Interviews in London. (Sept. 27th 1919 to Oct. 14th 1919.)" (copy), [1919 post-October 14] (Box 31, Folder 549)
    - [William Yale?]: memorandum re: "The Significance and Import of the Clemenceau-Lloyd George Agreement of September 1919,", [1919 October 14-31] (Box 31, Folder 550)
    - Cables re: Emir Feisal (copies), 1919 October 18, 20 (Box 31, Folder 551)
    - [William H. Buckler]: "Memorandum of [Polk's] Conversation with Abdul Hadi, Agent of Emir Feisal" (1919 Oct 17) and related correspondence (carbon with covering memorandum and enclosures), [1919 October 22?] (Box 31, Folder 552)
    - "Intelligence Report" re: "Rumanian, Russian, British, political and military situation in Near East" (copy), 1919 November 1 (Box 31, Folder 553)
    - Memorandum of conversation between T. E. Lawrence and an unnamed member of the American Mission re: Armenia, Turkey, Arabia, Syria, and the Jews, 1919 November 3, 19 (Box 31, Folder 554)
    - Frank L. Polk: memorandum of conversation with General Haddad re: relations with France (enclosing copies of correspondence between Feisal and Berthelot), 1919 November 25 - December 6 (Box 31, Folder 555)
  - Netherlands
    - Miscellaneous papers re: transmission of commercial messages, 1916-1918 (Box 31, Folder 556)
    - Memoranda re: trade (originals, carbons), 1917 May 23 - November 2, undated (Box 31, Folder 557)
    - Miscellaneous papers re: shipping, tonnage, 1917 (Box 31, Folder 558)
    - Cables exchanged with the American Legation, The Hague (copies), 1917-1918 (Box 31, Folder 559)
    - Miscellaneous papers re: trade, 1917-1918 (Box 31, Folder 560)
    - [Gordon Auchincloss?]: [draft memorandum?] re: Colonel House's recommendations about response to the Dutch attitude toward the League of Nations, [1918 September 6?] (Box 31, Folder 561)
    - Exchanges with the Dutch Legation, Washington, 1918 (Box 31, Folder 562)
    - [Draft public statements?] re: trade, [1918] (Box 31, Folder 563)
    - Miscellaneous papers re: Dutch citizens in the United States, 1919 March 4 - August 5 (Box 31, Folder 564)
  - Neutrals, Rights of
    - Joint State and Navy Neutrality Board: memorandum re: "revised draft of proposed legislation regarding neutrality and foreign relations" (carbon), 1916 April 7 (Box 31, Folder 565)
    - Memorandum for Congressman Fitzgerald re: violations of international law by belligerents (carbon), 1916 August 18 (Box 31, Folder 566)
    - Robert Lansing: letter to the President re: the treaties of 1783 and 1827 with Sweden and Norway (copy), 1918 March 18 (Box 31, Folder 567)
  - New Zealand
    - Cable to the American Consulate, Auckland (copy), 1918 May 14 (Box 31, Folder 568)
  - Nicaragua
    - Joshua B. Wright: memoranda re: Nicaraguan politics and the Nicaraguan treaty, 1915 December 15-20 (Box 31, Folder 569)
    - Miscellaneous papers re: election in Nicaragua, 1916 July 3-27 (Box 31, Folder 570)
  - Norway
    - H. H. Bryn: correspondence with Polk re: rights of neutrals, 1916 October 19-20 (Box 31, Folder 571)
    - Miscellaneous papers re: the Rationing Agreement, 1917 November 7 - 1918 October 24 (Box 31, Folder 572)
    - Memorandum re: "German Commercial Policy in Norway" (carbon), 1917 November 8 (Box 31, Folder 573)
    - Correspondence and related papers re: requisitioning Norwegian tonnage, 1917 November 8 - 1918 October 15 (Box 31, Folder 574)
    - Miscellaneous papers re: shipping, 1917 (Box 31, Folder 575)
    - Memorandum of Agreement between the War Trade Board of the United States of America and the Norwegian Government Relating to Exports from the United States to Norway, Dated April 30, 1918, 1918 [post-April 30] (Box 31, Folder 576)
    - Correspondence re: settlement of claims for requisitioned vessels, 1918-1919 (Box 31, Folder 577)
  - Palestine
    - Correspondence re: passports for American Zionists, 1918 February 28 - March 5 (Box 31, Folder 578)
  - Panama
    - Joshua Butler Wright: memoranda re: election in Panama, 1916 May 19, July 3 (Box 31, Folder 579)
    - Miscellaneous papers, 1916-1919 (Box 31, Folder 580)
    - Jordan H. Stabler: memoranda exchanged with Polk re: transfer of General Blatchford, [pre-1919 January 9] - 1919 January 24 (Box 31, Folder 581)
    - Elbridge G. Greene: memorandum re: conditions in Chiriqui, 1919 January 30 (Box 31, Folder 582)
    - Jordan H. Stabler: memoranda re: termination of the Panamanian lottery, 1919 January 30, February 8 (Box 31, Folder 583)
  - Passports
    - Correspondence and memoranda, 1915-1917 Oct, 1918 February - Nov, 1919 January - Oct, 1920 January - June (Box 31, Folder 584-590)
    - Miscellaneous papers re: Charles A. Beard, 1918 March 26-27, undated (Box 31, Folder 591)
  - Peace Efforts
    - Great Britain, Foreign Office: memorandum of conversation with Howard Taylor re: terms of settlement with Germany (copy), 1915 September 6 (Box 32, Folder 592)
    - Howard Taylor: correspondence with James Gerard and Eric Drummond re: terms of settlement with Germany (copies), 1915 September 6, 7 (Box 32, Folder 593)
    - Press releases (drafts, copies), 1916 May 10 - 1917 January 5, undated (Box 32, Folder 594)
    - Neutral Conference for Continuous Mediation: "Henry Ford and the Peace of Europe" (edited carbon), [1916 post-September 15] (Box 32, Folder 595)
    - Frank L. Polk: draft memorandum re: peace conference proposal, [1916] (Box 32, Folder 596)
    - Cables (copies; one annotated by Gordon Auchincloss), 1916-1917 (Box 32, Folder 597)
    - Department of State, Division of Information: Peace Overtures of the Central Powers and Reply of Entente Powers, 1917 February 15 (Box 32, Folder 598)
    - "Synopsis of Recent Information Received by the State Department Relative to Peace Proposals, Enemy Peace Propaganda, Etc., "no. 3 (carbon), 1918 September 25 (Box 32, Folder 599)
  - Persia
    - Miscellaneous papers, 1916-1919 (Box 32, Folder 600)
    - Louis H. Gray: memorandum to Polk re: "Request of the Persian Delegation for an Interview with You,", 1919 August 11 (Box 32, Folder 601)
    - John L. Caldwell: letter of introduction to Polk for the secretary of the Russian Legation, Teheran, 1919 September 8 (Box 32, Folder 602)
    - Louis H. Gray: memorandum re: "Correspondance [sic] concerning Anglo-Persian Agreement,", 1919 September 30 (Box 32, Folder 603)
    - Louis H. Gray: memorandum re: "Procedure of the American Minister at Teheran" in opposition to the Anglo-Persian Agreement, 1919 October 1 (Box 32, Folder 604)
    - Correspondence and memorandum of conversation between Polk and Prince Firouz, 1919 October 7-17 (Box 32, Folder 605)
    - Louis H. Gray: memorandum and draft letter re: "Conversation with Prince Firouz,", 1919 October 13, 17 (Box 32, Folder 605)
    - Persia, Minister of Foreign Affairs: letter to Polk transmitting copy of press release by the American Legation, Teheran, 1919 Sep 9, on the U.S. attitude toward Persian representation in Paris, 1919 October 13 (Box 32, Folder 606)
    - Cornelius van H. Engert: letter to John W. Davis re: conversation with Lord Curzon about the U.S. attitude toward the Anglo-Persian Agreement (copy), 1919 November 4 (Box 32, Folder 607)
  - Peru
    - Miscellaneous papers re: shipping, 1917-1918 (Box 32, Folder 608)
    - Memoranda, draft plan, and diplomatic note re: stabilization of exchange, 1918 September 21 - October 21 (Box 32, Folder 609)
    - Jordan H. Stabler: memoranda of conversations re: the Tacna-Arica dispute, 1918 December 3-18 (Box 32, Folder 610)
    - Memoranda re: raising the American Legation, Lima, to the rank of Embassy, 1918 December 10 - 1919 February 20 (Box 32, Folder 611)
    - Memoranda and letter to Wilson re: U.S. response to the disputed election of Augusto B. Leguia, 1919 July 18, 19 (Box 32, Folder 612)
    - Van Santvoord Merle-Smith: memorandum re: U.S. purchase of ex-German steamers Eten and Callao, 1920 March 19 (Box 32, Folder 613)
  - Petroleum
    - Economic Liaison Committee, Subcommittee on Mineral Raw Materials: "Summary of Facts and Recommendations bearing upon the Petroleum Policy of the United States" (mimeo), [1919 post-May 12] (Box 32, Folder 614)
    - Memorandum of meeting of the Council of National Defense, 1920 Mar 8, 1920 March 9 (Box 32, Folder 615)
    - Memorandum, "The British Ambassador's Remarks on Oil in his Speech at New York, May 25, 1920,", 1920 May 28 (Box 32, Folder 616)
  - Poland
    - Miscellaneous papers re: the Polish National Committee, 1917 October - 1918 May 28 (Box 32, Folder 617)
    - Miscellaneous papers re: Polish nationals in the United States, 1918 March 8, 26 (Box 32, Folder 618)
    - Roman Dmowski: memorandum re: postwar ambitions of Germany in Central Europe (copy), [pre-1918 November 11] (Box 32, Folder 619)
    - Commission Interalliée pour la Négociation d'un Armistice entre la Pologne et l'Ukraine: Procès-verbaux de la Commission et de la Sous-Commission de Rédaction; Rapport de la Commission, [1919 post-May 15] (Box 32, Folder 620)
    - Ellis L. Dresel: memorandum re: Polish manufacture of documents to show German secret activities, 1919 August 5 (Box 32, Folder 621)
    - Henry Morgenthau: letter to Ignacy Jan Paderewski re: proposal for an Allied loan, 1919 August 10 (Box 32, Folder 622)
    - Telegrams re: the military situation in Upper Silesia, 1919 August 18 - September 1 (Box 32, Folder 623)
    - Carpatho-Russian Committee: memorandum re: Polish treatment of Russians and Ruthenians in Eastern Galicia, 1919 August 23 (Box 32, Folder 624)